

"Trials & Errors! I seek to embrace challenges as opportunities to learn and amelor"

SKILLS

Postgre SQL

Microsoft Offices (PowerPoint, Excel, ...)

Tableau & Power BI

KNIME Analytics

SPSS

SAP ERP

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Premiere Pro

LANGUAGE

English - Fluent

French - Intermediate (DELF B1)

Vietnamese - Native

CONTACT



tieukbinh@gmail.com

Leuven 3010, Belgium

linkedin/tieukbinh

BINH TIEU

Junior Data Analyst

tieukbinh.github.io/BinhTieu-portfolio.github.io/

PROFILE

Teamwork | Intercultural communication | Business Insights | Data Analyse, Visualise, Report & Storytelling

PROJECT

GUEST EXPERIENCE & QUALITY MANAGEMENT

Radisson Hotel Group

- Analyse satisfaction & define influencing elements, then establish recommendations & actionable plans for improvement.

THE TLC TRIP RECORD DATA

PwC Belgium - Deals & Analytics

- Analyse big data using Tableau, understand consumer behaviours, consumption volume, gratuity pattern.

GRI & CQI YEAR-END REPORT

Radisson Hotel Group

- Benchmark RHG with competitors, benchmark subsidiary branches within RHG environments across various areas.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT-OF-HOUSE SUPERVISOR (PART-TIME)

Oct 2020 - Present | Hanoi Station, Brussels

- Handle a wide range of client interactions, resolving conflicts.
- Attention to details, manage guest's experience & requests.
- >> Developed strong interpersonal and problem-solving skills.

LEAD DIGITAL COMMUNICATION

Apr 2021 - Apr 2023 |

SIVIBI - Vietnamese Student Association in Belgium

- Guide & support team members for their own good.
- Strategise & coordinate output narratives.
- » Practiced leadership & enhance emotional intelligence.

HUMAN RESOURCE MANAGEMENT

Jan 2022 - Aug 2022 | Value Network, Leuven

- Optimise & automate database management systems.
- Interns & Volunteers acquisition and retention.
- > Improved workflow's efficiency & internal communication.

EDUCATION

DATA SCIENCE | MASTER OF BUSINESS MANAGEMENT

Universiteit Hasselt

MARKETING | BACHELOR OF BUSINESS MANAGEMENT

Odisee University College